Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this video, let's look at a few more utility methods present in the LocalDate class which help you to
在这段视频中，让我们看看LocalDate类中还有哪些实用的方法，它们可以帮助你
compare dates as well as set a specific value to a date.
比较日期，以及为一个日期设置一个特定的值。
So, until now we created a LocalDate object using LocalDate.now( ), right. So,
所以，到目前为止，我们使用LocalDate.now( )创建了一个LocalDate对象，对吧。所以。
what we did was LocalDate today = LocalDate.now( ).
我们所做的是 LocalDate today = LocalDate.now( )。
But there are other methods which are there which can be used to create specific dates. So, instead of
但是还有其他的方法，可以用来创建特定的日期。所以，代替
today,
今天。
let's say, I would want to hard code the date and get the details about yesterday. Yesterday was 31st,
比方说，我想对日期进行硬编码并获得昨天的详细信息。昨天是31号。
31st Jan.
1月31日。
So, for now, let's hardcode, I could have got 31st by subtracting one day from here.
所以，现在，让我们硬编码，我可以从这里减去一天，得到31号。
Let's hardcode the values now.
让我们现在来硬编码这些值。
So, there's a method called, of( ).
所以，有一个方法叫做，of( )。
I can say 2018 and I can say 01, 31. Oops!
我可以说2018年，我可以说01，31。哎呀!
I got something wrong.
我弄错了。
Okay, this is how it would be.
好吧，事情会是这样的。
So, yesterday, oops, I got the spelling wrong as well.
所以，昨天，哎呀，我把拼写也弄错了。
Okay.
好吧。
Yesterday is 2018-01-31.
昨天是2018-01-31。
So, this is one method which can set, help you to set a specific value.
所以，这是一个方法，可以设置，帮助你设置一个特定的值。
So, of( ) is a specific method in LocalDate which will help you to create a LocalDate instance, specifying
所以，of( )是LocalDate中的一个特定方法，它将帮助你创建一个LocalDate实例，指定
the specific year, month, and day.
具体的年、月、日。
So, now, today has this
所以，现在，今天有这个
and yesterday has this.
而昨天是这样的。
That's cool, right.
这很好，对吧。
There are methods which are present which would help you to set a specific year on this date.
有一些方法可以帮助你在这个日期上设置一个特定的年份。
So, I would want to find out the same day, but with a different year. I can say today.withYear,
所以，我想找出同样的日子，但不同的年份。我可以说 today.withYear。
I can say 2016, for example.
例如，我可以说是2016年。
So, it becomes 2016, the same day, first February in 2016 and you can also do today.with, a specific
所以，它就变成了2016年，同一天，2016年的第一个二月，你也可以做 today.with，一个特定的
day of the month.
月的某一天。
So, let's say I would want to have the date as of 20th day of this month.
所以，让我们说，我想把这个月的20日作为日期。
So, it would become 20 February 2018.
因此，它将成为2018年2月20日。
You can do the same thing with the month as well. So, you can say with today.withMonth( ) and say
你也可以对月份做同样的事情。所以，你可以用 today.withMonth( )说
I would want to be in the third month. The interesting method which is present in here is, today.with
我想在第三个月的时候。这里有一个有趣的方法，就是 today.with
DayOftheYear( ).
DayOftheYear( )。
You can say I would want the same year,
你可以说我想要同样的年份。
but with a specific day. So, 120th day of the year. So, it would return me 04-30.
但有一个特定的日子。所以，一年中的第120天。所以，它将返回给我04-30。
So, 30th April is the 120th day of 2018.
所以，4月30日是2018年的第120天。
So, what we are looking at in here is, we started off with looking at different way of creating the Local
所以，我们在这里看到的是，我们一开始就看到了创建本地的不同方式
Date with a specific date, month, and year and we are looking at, once you are having a specific date,
一旦你有了一个特定的日期，我们正在研究如何用一个特定的日期来修改它。
how do you modify it with a specific attribute.
你如何用一个特定的属性来修改它。
So, I would want to modify the year, or a month, or a day, or you would want to use the current year with a
所以，我想修改年、月、日，或者你想用当前的年和一年中的某一天。
specific day of the year.
特定的一年中的某一天。
So, these are all the options which are present in LocalDate to be able to do all these things.
所以，这些都是LocalDate中的所有选项，能够做所有这些事情。
One of the typical things that we would always do with dates is, we would want to compare.
我们总是对日期做的典型事情之一是，我们想进行比较。
Once you have two days, you'd want to compare whether they are before each other or after each other
一旦你有了两个日期，你就会想比较它们是在对方之前还是在对方之后
and there are methods to do that as well. So, you can do today.isBefore(yesterday).
也有一些方法可以做到这一点。所以，你可以做 today.isBefore(yesterday)。
Is that true?
那是真的吗？
false. today.isAfter(yesterday)
false。 today.isAfter(yesterday)
true.
为真。
So, this is to allow us to compare dates. So, isBefore( ) and isAfter( ) are two awesome methods to compare
所以，这是为了让我们能够比较日期。所以，isBefore( )和isAfter( )是两个很棒的方法来比较
dates as well.
日期的方法。
Whatever dates that we discussed on the LocalDate
我们在LocalDate上讨论的任何日期
class are also present on the LocalDateTime and the  LocalTime class as well. And, in LocalDateTime,
类中讨论过的日期，在LocalDateTime和LocalTime类中也都存在。而且，在LocalDateTime,
you'd also be able to do things like withHour, withMinute, withSecond, and things like that. So, you
你也可以做一些事情，比如与小时、与分钟、与秒，以及类似的事情。所以，你
can get specific things to manipulate hours, minutes, and seconds as well.
所以，你也可以得到特定的东西来操作小时、分钟和秒。
I'd leave that as an exercise for you to explore the LocalDateTime and the LocalTime APIs. In
我想把这个问题留给你去探索LocalDateTime和LocalTime APIs。在
this and the previous set of videos, we explored a wide variety of things related to the LocalDate, Local
和前一组视频中，我们探讨了与LocalDate、LocalDateTime和LocalTime类相关的各种各样的东西。
DateTime, and the LocalTime classes.
DateTime和LocalTime类。
We tried to play around with the dates and we tried to explore the API further.
我们尝试着玩弄日期，我们尝试着进一步探索API。
As I said before, exploring APIs is not really a fun thing.
正如我之前所说，探索API并不是一件真正有趣的事情。
It's a huge number of methods that you'd need to remember.
这是一个巨大的数字，你需要记住的方法。
So, try and remember, what are the operations you can do and if you want specific details or about a specific
所以，试着记住，你可以做哪些操作，如果你想要具体的细节或关于一个具体的
thing that you would want to do,
你想做的事情。
you can always a look at the Java docs of the API. All that you need to do is, if you want to search for
你可以随时看一下API的Java文档。你所需要做的就是，如果你想搜索
LocalDateTime,
LocalDateTime。
I would just need to say  java doc LocalDateTime and Java 9 and you'd be able to get the API and you can read
我只需要说java doc LocalDateTime和Java 9，你就可以得到API，你可以阅读
it and try and find out more about a specific class.
它，并尝试找出更多关于特定类的信息。
The most important thing for you is to remember that there is a specific class existing and probably
对你来说，最重要的是要记住有一个特定的类存在，并且可能
you can do a few things of this kind with that specific class.
你可以用那个特定的类做一些这样的事情。
Once you know that, once you are aware of that, you can locate the specific details from the documentation
一旦你知道了这一点，一旦你意识到了这一点，你就可以从API的文档中找到具体的细节。
of the API.
的具体细节。
I will see you in the next video.
我们将在下一个视频中见。